- May I join you, Leonard?
- Sure.
(Penny(off):)Thanks.
(Leonard:)Hey, Alex, let me ask you something.
(Leonard:)My girlfriend knows this guy at school.
He's got an English accent...
(Alex:)Ooh, I love English accents.
(Leonard:)Yeah, you all do.
(Leonard:)Anyway, I feel like he's hitting on her.
(Leonard:)She says he's just being nice
and I should trust her.
(Alex:)It's probably harmless.
(Alex:)You know how it is.
I'm sure you get hit on all the time.
(Leonard:)Right.
(Leonard:)Because girls are always like,
"Ooh, that guy owns two Star Trek uniforms...
(Leonard:)...and gets a lot of ear infections.
I gotta get me some of that."
(Raj:)I don't know.
Bet it happens more than you realize.
(Leonard:)Trust me, it doesn't.
(Raj:)You sure?
(Alex:)You're cute, you're funny.
(Alex:)Maybe you're getting hit on
and you don't even know it.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Leonard:)I'm pretty sure.